being a nerd is hard work you guys uh
but don't ask me I'm a fake geek girl
now there's a ton of comics so true
that's funny there's there's Comics to
read there's games to play there's so
many movies to watch people with bad
opinions online to argue with and now
suits to buy oppos suits just introduced
the Pac-Man suit now a lot of people
tweeted me this suit right here um which
I I really have to point out now this
legit looks like a suit people would
wear to my funeral uh
now I knew this would be remarkably on
brand for me but as a 44y old man who's
about to get married I I think maybe
maybe a head to toe Pac-Man suit is just
a little much at this point in my life
all right maybe I'm not going to do that
why yes I actually did buy the Pacman
suit after all um I'm sorry if it's hard
to hear me over your screaming genitalia
right now ladies and gentlemen this
arcade is
closed uh I I know what I said before
and the open of the show but the truth
of the matter is I bought this thing the
second it became
available and here it is and it's
[Applause]
amazing